<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Just Media, Inc.</title>
	<atom:link href="http://justmedia.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://justmedia.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 19:26:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.2.5</generator>
	<item>
		<title>If only I knew what other marketers are doing and how they are solving similar problems?”</title>
		<link>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/if-only-i-knew-what-other-marketers-are-doing-and-how-they-are-solving-similar-problems/</link>
		<comments>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/if-only-i-knew-what-other-marketers-are-doing-and-how-they-are-solving-similar-problems/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 06:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustAdmin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Dick Reed]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3484</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>If that statement has ever crossed your mind as you sit and contemplate your CMO’s most recent directive, then you are not alone. In a recent Just Media survey, the overwhelming feedback we received was that technology marketers are desperately looking to hear from their peers who share their pain in dealing with the ever&#8230;
<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/if-only-i-knew-what-other-marketers-are-doing-and-how-they-are-solving-similar-problems/" class="read-more-link">Read More &#8594;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/if-only-i-knew-what-other-marketers-are-doing-and-how-they-are-solving-similar-problems/">If only I knew what other marketers are doing and how they are solving similar problems?”</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/people.png"><img class="aligncenter wp-image-3491 size-full" src="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/people.png" alt="people" width="830" height="214" /></a></p>
<p>If that statement has ever crossed your mind as you sit and contemplate your CMO’s most recent directive, then you are not alone. In a recent Just Media survey, the overwhelming feedback we received was that technology marketers are desperately looking to hear from their peers who share their pain in dealing with the ever growing complexity of B2B technology marketing options.</p>
<p>With this in mind, together with our strategic partner Activate, <strong>Just Media is hosting an event on October 1st in Palo Alto, CA</strong>. Four marketers from different technology companies will address various marketing challenges and share their perspective and approach. The event is designed to be informative, educative and, most importantly, practical – helping marketers feel less isolated and more informed as they handle the challenges of evolving their own marketing mix. More details about the event can be <a href="http://www.justactivateevent.com/" target="_blank">found here</a>.</p>
<p>What will be covered you may ask. Again, based on the feedback from marketers, the biggest areas of interest (and pain) were:</p>
<ul>
<li>How to build a marketing infrastructure to maximize pipeline and revenue</li>
<li>How to maximize the conversions for leads being created currently</li>
<li>How to create compelling content to feed the marketing channels</li>
<li>How should content be selected, mapped, tracked and optimized across different channels like search, social, programmatic, nurture, etc.</li>
<li>A practical session covering how to approach Account Based Marketing by integrating multiple channels and data sets</li>
</ul>
<p>We look forward to seeing you there. For those who are unable to attend in person, please look out for associated whitepapers and hints &amp; tips post event to capture at least some of the essence of the content covered.</p>
<p><em>Please note due to restrictions on the number of attendees, this event is exclusively reserved for technology marketers ad pre-registration is required. Sign up early as there is a limited number of spaces.     </em></p>
<p><strong>Dick Reed<br />
</strong><b>Just Media, Inc.</b></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/if-only-i-knew-what-other-marketers-are-doing-and-how-they-are-solving-similar-problems/">If only I knew what other marketers are doing and how they are solving similar problems?”</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/if-only-i-knew-what-other-marketers-are-doing-and-how-they-are-solving-similar-problems/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Just Media’s New Motto Reflects The Timeless Impact of Media</title>
		<link>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/just-medias-new-motto-reflects-the-timeless-impact-of-media/</link>
		<comments>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/just-medias-new-motto-reflects-the-timeless-impact-of-media/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 00:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustAdmin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hillary Freeman]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3477</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Media Is The Means. Connecting People Is The Result. This is the motto, the driving inspiration of Just Media, and it means a lot more than meets the eye. It was a Wednesday morning during our weekly all-company meeting, when the power of what we do at Just Media became blatantly apparent.  “Now, don’t just&#8230;
<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/just-medias-new-motto-reflects-the-timeless-impact-of-media/" class="read-more-link">Read More &#8594;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/just-medias-new-motto-reflects-the-timeless-impact-of-media/">Just Media’s New Motto Reflects The Timeless Impact of Media</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/shutterstock_288888509.jpg"><img class=" size-medium wp-image-3478 aligncenter" src="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/shutterstock_288888509-300x200.jpg" alt="shutterstock_288888509" width="300" height="200" /></a></p>
<p><strong>Media Is The Means. Connecting People Is The Result.</strong> This is the motto, the driving inspiration of Just Media, and it means a lot more than meets the eye.</p>
<p>It was a Wednesday morning during our weekly all-company meeting, when the power of what we do at Just Media became blatantly apparent.  “Now, don’t just edit the lines in your email signature, I want everyone to have a think about what our new motto means,” Just Media’s CEO, Dick Reed, challenged, in his very British accent.</p>
<p>The motto – so simple, yet profound – instantly connected with me. Media connects people. My job, our job, in this fast-paced, whirlwind industry is to connect people. To provoke thought and promote growth, in all aspects of society, through interpersonal communication.</p>
<p>me∙di∙a<br />
/’mēdēə/<br />
Defined as “the main means of mass communication (broadcasting, publishing, and the internet), regarded collectively” (Oxford University Press, 2015). However, I feel like this broad definition does not go far enough to illustrate the true essence and impact of media.</p>
<p>Media clearly has many channels; it can have multiple goals and myriad effects, both positive and negative on society. However, its quintessential purpose and impact remains the same: Media allows people to disseminate information, share their messages, convey their ideas and engage with one another in open discussion. Connecting with other people is a cornerstone of life. It engenders change and growth.</p>
<p>The significance of media is colossal and dates back to society&#8217;s’ earliest origins. Throughout history, its primary purpose has been to connect people, to allow them to communicate. In America its roots lie in the very foundation of the nation: The Bill of Rights. The First Amendment grants the freedom of speech, freedom of the press and the right to peacefully assemble (The United States Bill of Rights,1791). It empowers the existence of free media, engendering a society of unrestricted interaction. The invention of Gutenberg&#8217;s Printing Press in 1436 allowed one message to multiply and be distributed to a mass audience, connecting people at a more rapid rate and a larger scale than ever before. This new form of media connected so many people that new ideologies developed, sparking the Protestant Reformation and scientific revolutions (New World Encyclopedia, 2015). Going way further back in time to 3000 B.C., the ancient Babylonians connected with one another through media using signs to advertise their stores (Beasley, R., &amp; Danesi, M. 2002). Legend has it, one of the first advertisements in existence was for prostitution. Now talk about that for connecting people! Media is a massive – and ancient, but ever-evolving – force inspiring human interaction.</p>
<p>In the modern world, media has become a much more powerful economic, political and social force. When media once was dominated by more traditional channels, such as print, live events, radio or even television, connection advanced at a slower rate. Now, with the Internet, programmatic platforms, and copious amounts of data, instantaneous interpersonal communication through an arsenal of devices has created a new kind of media universe. Now connecting people involves more precision, more strategy and a deeper, more sophisticated understanding of the 7.2 billion (U.S. Census Bureau, 2015) people on this earth.</p>
<p>Okay, you probably get it. Media is powerful, its old and it connects people. But how does display advertising in a largely dominated B2B environment connect people?  Sure a programmatic DSP can distribute information to someone, but how does it connect people?</p>
<p>Through media we are able to creatively craft and strategically place a message or piece of content, target an intended audience and deliver that information to those people. Media enables our clients to connect with people, whether he or she is a consumer or plays a decision-making role in his or her business. It allows our clients to initiate connections with people and inspire real engagement.</p>
<p>Connecting with people is not just a part of our daily routines or a function of our job. It is what we live, breathe, practice and preach. We proudly carry on the historic and unifying tradition of Media. Media and connecting with others is our passion. It is a powerful force, and here at Just Media we are the momentum behind that force.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Hillary Freeman<br />
</strong><strong>Just Media, Inc.</strong></p>
<p>Sources:</p>
<p>Beasley, R., &amp; Danesi, M. (2002). <em>Persuasive Signs: The semiotics of Advertising.</em> Berlin, Germany:  Walter de Gruyter GmbH &amp; Co. Retrieved from: https://books.google.com/books?id=xa0XWi1kg60C&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;source=gbs_ge_summary_r&amp;cad=0#v=onepage&amp;q&amp;f=false</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>New Wolrd Encyclopedia. (2015, June 2). Printing Press. Retrieved:  http://www.newworldencyclopedia.org/entry/Printing_press</p>
<p>Oxford University Press. (2015). Oxford Dictionaries. Language Matters. Retrieved from: http://www.oxforddictionaries.com/us/definition/american_english/media</p>
<p>The United States Bill of Rights. (1791, December 15). Retrieved from:  http://www.archives.gov/exhibits/charters/bill_of_rights_transcript.html</p>
<p>The United States Census Bureau. (2015). U.S. and World Population Clock. Retrieved from: http://www.census.gov/popclock/</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/just-medias-new-motto-reflects-the-timeless-impact-of-media/">Just Media’s New Motto Reflects The Timeless Impact of Media</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/just-medias-new-motto-reflects-the-timeless-impact-of-media/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Don’t Cry Over Blocked Banners, Use Content Instead</title>
		<link>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/dont-cry-over-blocked-banners-use-content-instead/</link>
		<comments>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/dont-cry-over-blocked-banners-use-content-instead/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 18:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustAdmin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Jade Natal]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3471</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Did you hear? Banner advertising as we know it is dead. I know that I’m not the only one who has seen the countless articles prophesying an online display advertising apocalypse, most notably covered in the New York Times and Fortune magazine. This imminent end is due in large part to the increased use of&#8230;
<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/dont-cry-over-blocked-banners-use-content-instead/" class="read-more-link">Read More &#8594;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/dont-cry-over-blocked-banners-use-content-instead/">Don’t Cry Over Blocked Banners, Use Content Instead</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/shutterstock_215270242.jpg"><img class="aligncenter wp-image-3474 size-medium" src="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/shutterstock_215270242-300x195.jpg" alt="shutterstock_215270242" width="300" height="195" /></a></p>
<p>Did you hear? Banner advertising as we know it is dead.</p>
<p>I know that I’m not the only one who has seen the countless articles prophesying an online display advertising apocalypse, most notably covered in the <a href="http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/08/10/study-of-ad-blocking-software-suggests-wide-use/?_r=0" target="_blank">New York Times</a> and <a href="http://fortune.com/2015/08/13/publishers-only-have-themselves-to-blame-for-the-ad-blocking-apocalypse/" target="_blank">Fortune magazine</a>. This imminent end is due in large part to the increased use of consumer ad-blocking technology. While the use of ad-blockers is concerning on multiple fronts, it seems a bit preemptive to declare an entire industry at death’s door.</p>
<p>This consumer-driven movement towards a more ad-free user experience is a sign that brands and advertisers need to start looking for <a href="http://www.justmedia.com/2015/09/mobile-advertising-forced-to-go-beyond-banners/" target="_blank">more creative and unique ways</a> to reach their audience. Even before the recent surge in ad-blocking technology, banner blindness was already an issue. The reality today is that ad banners are simply becoming less effective as a standalone advertising source. To me, the whole situation brings to mind the famous saying by Winston Churchill, “Now this is not the end. It is not even the beginning of the end. But it is, perhaps, the end of the beginning.”</p>
<p>Content marketing and inbound tactics that support it like native advertising and social media are already being used successfully as alternatives to traditional banner advertising. Having a strong content marketing strategy has always been essential, but the recent fire and brimstone sentiment makes it even more crucial to know how to use content as part of a holistic digital program. Creating original, audience-driven assets that speak to specific pain points and offer genuinely useful insights is one of the best ways to offset banner blindness, cultivate stronger relationships,  and build brand association.</p>
<p>According to a study by Axonn Media, <a href="http://kapost.com/content-marketing-facts/" target="_blank">70% of consumers</a> actually prefer to get to know a company via articles rather than ads. We go to our favorite sites to consume content, so it makes sense that relevant brand-generated material in a native format feels less invasive. The content you create acts as its own filter since the audience can self-select what they want to read and what they don’t. Most importantly, your content strategy should center on enhancing a user’s experience—not interrupting it—when they browse the web.</p>
<p>In reality, banner advertising is probably not going away any time soon. But it would be remiss not to see recent events as an opportunity to innovate. Good content has always been a valuable tool in the digital marketing arsenal, but now it is more important than ever.</p>
<p><strong><br />
Jade Natal<br />
</strong><strong>Just Media, Inc.</strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/dont-cry-over-blocked-banners-use-content-instead/">Don’t Cry Over Blocked Banners, Use Content Instead</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/dont-cry-over-blocked-banners-use-content-instead/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amid Growth, #Instagram Rolls Out New Advertising Formats</title>
		<link>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/amid-growth-instagram-rolls-out-new-advertising-formats/</link>
		<comments>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/amid-growth-instagram-rolls-out-new-advertising-formats/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 19:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustAdmin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Annie Nguyen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Instagram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Instagram Ads]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3463</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Instagram is planning on rolling out advertising opportunities to all marketers, which will mean more ads in our photo feeds.  As an avid Instagram user, I’ve noticed that I’ll get 1-2 branded ads on my news feed every day.  Instagram currently showcases a select amount of ads from big brands, allowing a handful of large&#8230;
<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/amid-growth-instagram-rolls-out-new-advertising-formats/" class="read-more-link">Read More &#8594;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/amid-growth-instagram-rolls-out-new-advertising-formats/">Amid Growth, #Instagram Rolls Out New Advertising Formats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Instagram is planning on rolling out advertising opportunities to all marketers, which will mean more ads in our photo feeds.  As an avid Instagram user, I’ve noticed that I’ll get 1-2 branded ads on my news feed every day.  Instagram currently showcases a select amount of ads from big brands, allowing a handful of large brands to <em>place carefully drafted messaging to the Instagram audience</em>. Within the next few weeks, we can expect to see many more ads for Instagram as they are opening their sponsored feed posts to all advertisers.  Within the next two years, Instagram will earn roughly <a href="http://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/254885/instagrams-mobile-ad-revenues-to-hit-nearly-3b-b.html">$2.81 billion through advertising revenue alone</a>. From the mom and pop coffee shop to large businesses like Nike, Inc., every marketer will have the chance to advertise on Instagram.  To help advertisers reach the right audience, Instagram is working to make <a href="http://blog.business.instagram.com/post/120537653811/the-next-steps-for-ads-on-instagram-new-formats">advertisement available through an Instagram Ads API</a> and Facebook ad buying interface in the near future according to a blog on Instagram’s website.</p>
<p>Instagram is incorporating hashtags to help advertisers hone in on who they are targeting. With the handy use of hashtags, users will be able to search relative topics and find exactly what they are looking for.  In addition, instead of seeing a single creative, Instagram created carousel ads where users can swipe through four different creatives. This helps advertisers showcase a wider variety of topics and also create a story for the users to help them become more engaged with the ads.  Most advertisers leave the last slide for a call to action and a link to a branded page. Since June 1<sup>st</sup>, Instagram has <a href="http://www.adweek.com/socialtimes/instagram-carousel-ads-global/620923">expanded their advertising to six additional countries</a>, which includes UK, Canada, Australia, Germany, France, and Brazil.</p>
<p>Marketers will be able to target their audience not just by their age and gender, but also target user interests, activities on Instagram and the people they follow.  Instagram has always attracted a younger audience compared to that of Facebook, and these new advertising opportunities will allow brands to hone in on their targeting to young adults and teenagers.</p>
<p>As part of a media agency, I find it fascinating and exciting to see how Instagram advertisement will develop over the next two years.  On the other hand, from the viewpoint of an Instagram user, the thought of seeing more ads on my newsfeed is a bit overwhelming. In a quote given to New York Times, Instagram’s Global Head of Business and Brand Development, James Quarles said “<em>Visual storytelling for brands has more resonance. People remember it more. But we want to make sure the ads they see are for things that matter to them.</em>” With the right execution and creativity, users could be interested in the ads that they start to see in their photo feeds. By having the ability to target user by interests, marketers can reach their target audience and hope to get users engaged with their messaging and brand. Instagram is currently working on giving users the ability to click on an image and directly link them to a product page or an app install page.  Say goodbye to copying and pasting URLs into a browser and say hello to simple clicking! By 2019, we can expect to see over one third of the country using social media.</p>
<p><strong>Annie Nguyen<br />
</strong><strong>Just Media, Inc.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Sources:</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://www.fashiontimes.com/articles/22719/20150728/instagram-expected-earn-more-mobile-advertising-revenue-google-2017.htm">http://www.fashiontimes.com/articles/22719/20150728/instagram-expected-earn-more-mobile-advertising-revenue-google-2017.htm</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/254885/instagrams-mobile-ad-revenues-to-hit-nearly-3b-b.html">http://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/254885/instagrams-mobile-ad-revenues-to-hit-nearly-3b-b.html</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2015/06/03/technology/instagram-to-announce-plans-to-expand-advertising.html?_r=0">http://www.nytimes.com/2015/06/03/technology/instagram-to-announce-plans-to-expand-advertising.html?_r=0</a></p>
<p><a href="http://blog.business.instagram.com/post/120537653811/the-next-steps-for-ads-on-instagram-new-formats">http://blog.business.instagram.com/post/120537653811/the-next-steps-for-ads-on-instagram-new-formats</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="http://www.altimetergroup.com/2015/07/why-instagram-will-outsell-google-and-twitters-display-advertising-by-2017/">http://www.altimetergroup.com/2015/07/why-instagram-will-outsell-google-and-twitters-display-advertising-by-2017/</a></p>
<p><a href="http://mobilemarketingmagazine.com/instagram-mobile-ad-revenues-beat-google-twitter">http://mobilemarketingmagazine.com/instagram-mobile-ad-revenues-beat-google-twitter</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.socialmediatoday.com/social-business/adhutchinson/2015-07-28/instagram-generate-281-billion-10-facebooks-overall-ad">http://www.socialmediatoday.com/social-business/adhutchinson/2015-07-28/instagram-generate-281-billion-10-facebooks-overall-ad</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/254885/instagrams-mobile-ad-revenues-to-hit-nearly-3b-b.html">http://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/254885/instagrams-mobile-ad-revenues-to-hit-nearly-3b-b.html</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/amid-growth-instagram-rolls-out-new-advertising-formats/">Amid Growth, #Instagram Rolls Out New Advertising Formats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/amid-growth-instagram-rolls-out-new-advertising-formats/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mobile Advertising Forced to Go Beyond Banners</title>
		<link>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/mobile-advertising-forced-to-go-beyond-banners/</link>
		<comments>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/mobile-advertising-forced-to-go-beyond-banners/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2015 17:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustAdmin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Diana Nguyen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Advertising]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3431</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The last time the New York Times was in the news (instead of the source of news), I was appalled and confused by their suggestion that readers add peas to guacamole. Recently, however, the so-called guacamole ruining publisher was in the news for something that won me back –their latest native mobile advertising offerings. Native&#8230;
<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/mobile-advertising-forced-to-go-beyond-banners/" class="read-more-link">Read More &#8594;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/mobile-advertising-forced-to-go-beyond-banners/">Mobile Advertising Forced to Go Beyond Banners</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The last time the New York Times was in the news (instead of the source of news), I was appalled and confused by their suggestion that readers add <a href="http://cooking.nytimes.com/recipes/1015047-green-pea-guacamole">peas to guacamole</a>. Recently, however, the so-called guacamole ruining publisher was in the news for something that won me back –their latest native mobile advertising offerings. Native advertising and mobile advertising are certainly not new ideas, and neither is native mobile advertising. But, with the increased use of ad-blocking software, publishers now have to circumvent the lost revenue by turning to native ad units. At the moment, it is interesting to observe why and how publishers are being forced to deal with the growing distaste for mobile banner ads and the successes of native advertising in its place.</p>
<p>First, let’s review why it is necessary for publishers to shift their mobile revenue focus from banner units to native units. During this year’s Worldwide Developers Conference, Apple announced that <a href="https://www.apple.com/ios/ios9-preview/">iOS9</a>, the new operating system for iPhones and iPads, will include an <a href="http://www.theverge.com/2015/6/11/8764437/iphone-adblock-safari-ios-9">adblock feature</a>. According to a <a href="http://blog.pagefair.com/2014/adblocking-report/">2014 study by Adobe</a>, there are already 140 million adblock users around the world who manually installed the feature. If Apple includes the feature on iPhones and iPads, many more users will likely opt-out of being served those pesky mobile ads that seem impossible to exit.</p>
<p>Another reason why publishers are retiring most mobile banner ads is to improve user experience. Most mobile phones do not have enough space for banner ads, so the ads take up more of the screen than users would like. Users may get frustrated as they unsuccessfully attempt to close the ad and end up leaving the page all together. Even advertisers tend to steer away from mobile ads. DigiDay wrote, “Mobile’s combination of poor targeting and tracking capabilities and lackluster creative opportunities have given advertisers no real reason to invest in the medium.” For publishers, mobile ads are not the highest valued units either. Most mobile ad inventory is sold through exchanges and networks (<a href="http://digiday.com/publishers/celtraes-days-numbered-mobile-banner/">Marshall</a>), driving the costs down and generating low revenues. Needless to say, mobile banner ads are not popular and publishers need to find an alternative fast.</p>
<p>With the demand for higher quality mobile ad units, many publishers are challenged to think outside of the box and come up with creative ways to expand their mobile advertising offerings. From June of 2014 to June of 2015, the number of apps using native ads increased by eightfold (figure 1). Big-name publishers, such as the New York Times and Yahoo, are retiring the interruptive mobile banner ads and introducing new mobile ad formats. Many of the new formats will mimic the in-feed content ads that have been standard on Facebook and Twitter. With publishers’ amplified efforts to improve mobile ads, users will likely find their user experiences more enjoyable.</p>
<p>For example, the New York Times will soon be releasing an offering called Mobile Moments, which will customize ads to align with the seven moments in a day that are most important to its readers (<a href="http://adage.com/article/media/york-times-plans-add-mobile-native-ads-september/299814/">Peterson</a>). Ads served in the early mornings will be text-based to match text heavy news articles. In the evenings, when news articles are presented in more entertaining layouts, ads will be served with pictures and videos. With the ability to choose which moment of the day to target ads, advertisers might be more inclined to buy these mobile ad units directly rather than through an exchange or network. By putting more thought into improving user experience and creating valuable mobile ad units, publishers increase their opportunities to have direct relationships with advertisers and keep audiences satisfied.</p>
<p>The benefits of offering native units are abundant so publishers and app developers should be motivated to think beyond the basics with native mobile advertising. During SXSW in Austin, Texas, <a href="http://www.adweek.com/adfreak/tinder-users-sxsw-are-falling-woman-shes-not-what-she-appears-163486">Tinder’s native campaign</a> created an account for an AI character in the movie and allowed users to match with her, talk to her, and eventually discover she was a robot. The advertisement seamlessly fit with Tinder’s unique look and feel, while still staying true to the central theme of the movie and target audience. Like Tinder, many publishers and app developers are blending research and creativity to create and offer ads units without the limitation of standard specifications. It will be fascinating to observe how native mobile advertising will expand over the next couple years, now that publishers are moving far beyond the standard mobile banners ads.</p>
<p><strong>Diana Nguyen<br />
</strong><strong>Just Media, Inc.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Sources:</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://adage.com/article/media/york-times-plans-add-mobile-native-ads-september/299814/">http://adage.com/article/media/york-times-plans-add-mobile-native-ads-september/299814/</a></p>
<p><a href="http://nativeadvertisinginstitute.com/blog/three-storylines-from-the-week-in-native-advertising-3/">http://nativeadvertisinginstitute.com/blog/three-storylines-from-the-week-in-native-advertising-3/</a></p>
<p><a href="http://nativeadvertisinginstitute.com/blog/while-apple-shuts-down-mobile-advertising-native-might-soar/">http://nativeadvertisinginstitute.com/blog/while-apple-shuts-down-mobile-advertising-native-might-soar/</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/249906/why-publishers-prefer-native-advertising.html">http://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/249906/why-publishers-prefer-native-advertising.html</a></p>
<p><a href="http://blog.pagefair.com/2014/adblocking-report/%20%20">http://blog.pagefair.com/2014/adblocking-report/ </a></p>
<p><a href="http://digiday.com/publishers/celtraes-days-numbered-mobile-banner/">http://digiday.com/publishers/celtraes-days-numbered-mobile-banner/</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.adweek.com/adfreak/tinder-users-sxsw-are-falling-woman-shes-not-what-she-appears-163486">http://www.adweek.com/adfreak/tinder-users-sxsw-are-falling-woman-shes-not-what-she-appears-163486</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/09/mobile-advertising-forced-to-go-beyond-banners/">Mobile Advertising Forced to Go Beyond Banners</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://justmedia.com/2015/09/mobile-advertising-forced-to-go-beyond-banners/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Is Happening To The Destination URL Report in AdWords?</title>
		<link>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/what-is-happening-to-the-destination-url-report-in-adwords/</link>
		<comments>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/what-is-happening-to-the-destination-url-report-in-adwords/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 18:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustAdmin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Adam Nesicolaci]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdWords]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Destination URL]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3420</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>As most search marketers know by now, the roll out of Upgraded URL&#8217;s in AdWords, is in full swing. Any new ads that have been created in July are using the Upgraded URL&#8217;s format (Final URL + Tracking Template) rather than the classic, Destination URL&#8217;s we have come to know and maybe not love. So&#8230;
<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/what-is-happening-to-the-destination-url-report-in-adwords/" class="read-more-link">Read More &#8594;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/what-is-happening-to-the-destination-url-report-in-adwords/">What Is Happening To The Destination URL Report in AdWords?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/GoogleAdwords.png"><img class=" size-medium wp-image-3456 aligncenter" src="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/GoogleAdwords-300x207.png" alt="GoogleAdwords" width="300" height="207" /></a></p>
<p>As most search marketers know by now, the roll out of Upgraded URL&#8217;s in AdWords<span style="text-decoration: line-through;">,</span> is in full swing. Any new ads that have been created in July are using the Upgraded URL&#8217;s format (Final URL + Tracking Template) rather than the classic, Destination URL&#8217;s we have come to know and maybe not love.</p>
<p>So far the roll out has been somewhat smooth. Editing your tracking information in the final URL is fairly straightforward and does not trigger a complete review of your ad, keeping all your data intact (a very nice feature.)</p>
<p>Unfortunately, one problem that has been plaguing Search Marketers is the absence of any reporting at the URL level.</p>
<p>Our team has a number of client reports that utilize the Destination URL report to pull in raw data. This past month we found that all of the new ads we have created that utilize Upgraded URLs are not present on this report.</p>
<p>When asked, a representative from Google assured us that there will be a Final URL report feature launched, but the time frame is still unknown.</p>
<p><strong>How Can You Report on URL Tracking Parameters?</strong></p>
<p>So then, what can you do in the meantime? How can you report on URL tracking parameters in the days of the disappearing Destination URL Report?</p>
<p>You can use labels.</p>
<p>Label all new ads that are created to quickly organize and view relevant info on performance and spend.</p>
<p>For example, in the past, you may have used the utm_campaign parameter to filter your Destination URL report. Now, when launching new ads you should consider labeling your ads based on the parameters that you need to filter by. It is an extra step, but one that can save you the heartache of realizing that you can no longer filter your data by UTM parameters (at least until Google comes up with a replacement for the Destination URL Report). You can then use this to supplement any data that is pulled in from the Upgraded URL report.</p>
<p>Check back for updates regarding any new information that will be coming out on the Final URL report!</p>
<p><strong><br />
Adam Nesicolaci<br />
</strong><strong>Just Media, Inc.</strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/what-is-happening-to-the-destination-url-report-in-adwords/">What Is Happening To The Destination URL Report in AdWords?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/what-is-happening-to-the-destination-url-report-in-adwords/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Just Media: Finalists in the 2015 Content Marketing Institute Awards</title>
		<link>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/just-media-finalists-in-the-2015-content-marketing-institute-awards/</link>
		<comments>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/just-media-finalists-in-the-2015-content-marketing-institute-awards/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustAdmin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Brandon Friesen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Content Marketing Awards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finalist]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Just News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3409</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s always tough to make a mark when you first submit in a new category, but the Just Media team was proud to be recognized as a finalist in the recently announced Content Marketing Awards 2015 in the category of Best Paid Advertising / Content Marketing Integration. The project submitted was the cobranded Intel /&#8230;
<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/just-media-finalists-in-the-2015-content-marketing-institute-awards/" class="read-more-link">Read More &#8594;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/just-media-finalists-in-the-2015-content-marketing-institute-awards/">Just Media: Finalists in the 2015 Content Marketing Institute Awards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s always tough to make a mark when you first submit in a new category, but the Just Media team was proud to be recognized as a finalist in the recently announced Content Marketing Awards 2015 in the category of Best Paid Advertising / Content Marketing Integration.</p>
<p>The project submitted was the cobranded Intel / Amazon Web Services (AWS) content marketing program called Cloud Insights (<a href="http://www.cloudinsights.com">www.cloudinsights.com</a>). The Just Media team developed a communications strategy that successfully used a paid, content-based digital media strategy to distribute content from the central hub to a highly engaged audience of IT and business decision makers. In every phase of the campaign, hyper-optimizations across channels allowed the team to surpass all reach, engagement and conversion goals.</p>
<p>Using a combination of native ad platforms, programmatic media, content-based display units, paid search and various forms of targeting / retargeting, the team distributed snackable content, such as technology articles, blogs and case studies taken from a range of fascinating Intel / AWS deployments from organizations including NASA, Unilver and Aerospace Corporation. Once initial content engagement was made with the target audience, users were then prompted to take deeper actions, thus aligning both brand and demand goals.</p>
<p>Key collaborators included Portland-based creative shop Quango, Inc., who led design efforts, RebelMouse, whose platform hosted the hub, and IDG Marketing Services for content creation.</p>
<p>To deliver on such a comprehensive mix of media tactics for the project, Just Media leveraged an in-house team of media experts including the content, search, social, programmatic and digital specialists.  It was this degree of integration across multiple paid digital channels that really caught the eye of the judges, since it demonstrated Just’s ability to be channel agnostic given it has experts across all digital media fields.</p>
<p>“Just Media’s goal is to never let our clients use of digital channels be compromised by our own limitations as an organization. Content marketing in its latest form is newer to the market, but Just Media is an early adopter with tests in the market for years, leveraging the earliest of the latest wave of native offerings,” said CEO Dick Reed. “We have heavily invested in staff and technologies that now enable us to deliver the complex omni-channel strategies our clients demand.”</p>
<p>In the last 18 months Just’s client roster has more than doubled, as has its number of employees, and nowhere has that growth been more evident than in content creation, curation and marketing.</p>
<p>Congratulations to all CMA participants, finalists and winners!</p>
<p><strong>Brandon Friesen<br />
</strong><strong>Just Media, Inc.</strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/just-media-finalists-in-the-2015-content-marketing-institute-awards/">Just Media: Finalists in the 2015 Content Marketing Institute Awards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/just-media-finalists-in-the-2015-content-marketing-institute-awards/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do consumers trust the government more than big business with personal data? Does it matter?</title>
		<link>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/do-consumers-trust-the-government-more-than-big-business-with-personal-data-does-it-matter/</link>
		<comments>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/do-consumers-trust-the-government-more-than-big-business-with-personal-data-does-it-matter/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 17:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustAdmin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[David Wekselbaum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Privacy]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3406</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>According to TRUSTe’s 2014 study, the answer may be a bit more complicated. 58% of users concerned with online privacy choose “Business sharing my personal information with other companies” as the primary reason for their concern. 38% of users chose “reports of government surveillance” as the primary cause. Overall 92% of internet users worry about&#8230;
<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/do-consumers-trust-the-government-more-than-big-business-with-personal-data-does-it-matter/" class="read-more-link">Read More &#8594;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/do-consumers-trust-the-government-more-than-big-business-with-personal-data-does-it-matter/">Do consumers trust the government more than big business with personal data? Does it matter?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to <a href="https://www.truste.com/resources/privacy-research/us-consumer-confidence-index-2014/">TRUSTe’s 2014 study</a>, the answer may be a bit more complicated. 58% of users concerned with online privacy choose “Business sharing my personal information with other companies” as the primary reason for their concern. 38% of users chose “reports of government surveillance” as the primary cause. Overall 92% of internet users worry about their online privacy, with 47% of users indicating their worry is frequent or always. This means advertisers are theoretically entering the market with virtually every user’s guard up.</p>
<p>Concerns from users regarding privacy aren’t new. Pushback from government regulators sparked a rapid response from the online marketing industry to self-regulate and show a greater level of transparency to consumers. Most notably, the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) created the <a href="http://www.youradchoices.com/">Ad Choices program</a> in 2010. The triangular icon placed in the top right corner of banners served from Online Behavioral Advertising (OBA) gives consumers information on how they were targeted, as well as how to opt-out of cookie tracking.</p>
<p>Many in the industry question whether this seemingly ubiquitous distrust in online advertising matters when it comes to the bottom line performance. Users are concerned, sure, but are they actively looking to opt out? Do they care enough to seek out the relevant information? <a href="http://ksmmedia.com/files/1714/2971/8322/Spring_2015_SOM_KSM_CHI.pdf">Studies suggest</a> 74% of users are unaware of AdChoices and the ability to opt-out of behavioral tracking.</p>
<p>Advertisers may be aware of the problem, but seem unclear on a solution. A <a href="http://www.doubleverify.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/02/OBA_paper.pdf">recent study</a> by the Ponemon Institute, a trust and privacy research organization, found that though 70% of online marketers agree OBA increases marketing performance, 98% of the same marketers polled agree that privacy concerns limit spending on OBA.</p>
<p><strong>Fear the Smartphone</strong></p>
<p>Trust issues continue on mobile as well. 80% of smartphone users actively avoid apps perceived to have poor privacy protection. Mobile advertising traffic is increasing at a rapid rate, and so is the level of concern amongst users.</p>
<p>To combat this, as of September 1, 2015, the DAA is requiring all participating interest-based advertising on mobile to require the same Ad Choices logo as desktop, along with a link to privacy policies and opt-out information. It will be interesting to track how an expansion to mobile will affect the overall exposure of Ad Choices as an advocacy tool.</p>
<p><strong>Rising Concerns</strong></p>
<p>As privacy concerns among users continue to rise, advertisers cannot ignore this shift in the long run. Performance is strong in Online Behavioral Advertising, but advertisers are increasingly worried about turning more users off with privacy invasion. The Ad Choices campaign is a solid attempt at informing more users about behavioral targeting, but it is imperative that the industry do more.</p>
<p>If we don’t adapt and address concerns, we run the risk of the powers that be making the rules for us.</p>
<p><strong><br />
David Wekselbaum<br />
</strong><b>Just Media, Inc.</b></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/do-consumers-trust-the-government-more-than-big-business-with-personal-data-does-it-matter/">Do consumers trust the government more than big business with personal data? Does it matter?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/do-consumers-trust-the-government-more-than-big-business-with-personal-data-does-it-matter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Social Media: Today&#8217;s Go-To News Source</title>
		<link>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/social-media-the-go-to-news-source/</link>
		<comments>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/social-media-the-go-to-news-source/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 17:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustAdmin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Cindy Nguy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cecil the Lion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3388</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, news really does travel fast. The power of social media has rapidly increased our access to current events and everything in between. For example, the recent killing of Cecil the Lion in Zimbabwe by an American dentist went from zero to viral in less than 24 hours via social media. On Facebook alone, articles&#8230;
<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/social-media-the-go-to-news-source/" class="read-more-link">Read More &#8594;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/social-media-the-go-to-news-source/">The Power of Social Media: Today&#8217;s Go-To News Source</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today, news really does travel fast. The power of social media has rapidly increased our access to current events and everything in between. For example, the recent killing of Cecil the Lion in Zimbabwe by an American dentist went from zero to viral in less than 24 hours via social media. On Facebook alone, articles were re-posted, commented, and shared about how the hunter, Walter Palmer, paid over $50,000 to hunt a lion that was a beloved figure of Hwange Park. The news infuriated many people to the point where Palmer’s business Yelp page, his Facebook page, and even his personal voicemail were flooded with angry comments, eventually forcing him to shut down his dental office.</p>
<p>Social media has gone beyond just another pathway to access news—in many ways it now has the power to make the news. In the wake of the Cecil the Lion story and the tidal wave of responses that followed, it is hard to image that this would have gotten the same level of attention if these social platforms had not existed.  More and more people now use social media as their core source for current events. Breaking news is now shared via the social community faster than traditional news outlets can report on it. According to a 2013 PEW Research Study, 64% US adults are on Facebook regularly, with 30% of this audience also getting their news directly from the platform.</p>
<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/SocialMediaPathwayToNews1.png"><img class="aligncenter wp-image-3400 size-full" src="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/SocialMediaPathwayToNews1.png" alt="SocialMediaPathwayToNews" width="449" height="532" /></a></p>
<p>While the Cecil the Lion story serves as an example of the negative power of social media, these channels continue to provide a captive and highly engaged audience. In the US, an average of 40 minutes is being spent daily on Facebook alone.  Although the audience is inundated with news and events through their social feeds, they still take the time to engage with content that catches their attention. If it’s compelling content, users are more likely to respond and take some sort of action (comment, share the article, or look for more information).</p>
<p>Given the amount of time users spend on these social media platforms and how engage they can be, there is definitely a big opportunity for marketers to interact with their audience via social channels. Additionally, targeting capabilities are becoming more and more advanced to help with reaching the right audience at the right time, and ultimately get them to take a desired action—whether it’s making a purchase or engaging with your brand further.</p>
<p>Today, social media is a powerful and viral vehicle that is increasingly becoming a major source for news, and most importantly another way for brands to engage with their audience.</p>
<p><strong>Cindy Nguy<br />
</strong><strong>Just Media, Inc.</strong></p>
<p>Sources:</p>
<p>http://www.journalism.org/2013/11/14/news-use-across-social-media-platforms/</p>
<p>http://www.businessinsider.com/how-much-time-people-spend-on-facebook-per-day-2015-7</p>
<p>http://www.redding.com/business/nerd-chick-adventures-social-media-and-internet-backlash-with-cecil-the-lion-more_36942653</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/08/social-media-the-go-to-news-source/">The Power of Social Media: Today&#8217;s Go-To News Source</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://justmedia.com/2015/08/social-media-the-go-to-news-source/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mobile Marketing: The New King</title>
		<link>http://justmedia.com/2015/07/mobile-marketing-the-new-king/</link>
		<comments>http://justmedia.com/2015/07/mobile-marketing-the-new-king/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 16:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustAdmin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Amy Recuero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Programmatic]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=3322</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re not already in mobile, you’re behind – and here’s why: According to Marketo’s Definitive Guide to Mobile Marketing, “79% of Smartphone users have their phone on, or near them, for all but two hours of their waking day.” They go on to report this staggering figure:  There are 7.1 billion people on Earth,&#8230;
<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/2015/07/mobile-marketing-the-new-king/" class="read-more-link">Read More &#8594;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/07/mobile-marketing-the-new-king/">Mobile Marketing: The New King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/Mobile-Marketing.jpg"><img class=" size-medium wp-image-3323 aligncenter" src="http://justmedia.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/Mobile-Marketing-300x200.jpg" alt="Mobile Marketing" width="300" height="200" /></a></p>
<p>If you’re not already in mobile, you’re behind – and here’s why:</p>
<p>According to Marketo’s Definitive Guide to Mobile Marketing, “79% of Smartphone users have their phone on, or near them, for all but two hours of their waking day.” They go on to report this staggering figure:  There are 7.1 billion people on Earth, and 7.7 billion mobile devices. In order to reach today’s customer, advertisers must consider mobile marketing.</p>
<p>Infiltrating the mobile arena is also important for publishers. All the major players are buying or have bought mobile ad networks: from Google acquiring InMobi, to Yahoo picking up Flurry, or AOL <a href="http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2015-07-09/millennial-media-jumps-on-reported-aol-purchase-talks" target="_blank">in talks</a> to snag Millennial Media, the race is on to dominate mobile from all sides.</p>
<p>A key component to mobile marketing is programmatic. Programmatic accounted for 45% of overall ad spend last year (10 billion dollars), and is predicted to double that figure by 2016. Out of that 10 billion, programmatic mobile spend took 44% of the pie. One can only imagine as marketers and publishers continue to improve granular data targeting, workarounds for cookie deletion, responsive design and other nuances to mobile advertising, marketing budgets will most likely shift over much more rapidly.</p>
<p><strong>However, programmatic advertising</strong> is not new, not to us at least. Here at Just Media, we have seen it evolve from the <a href="http://justmedia.com/2008/06/automated-media-buying-is-this-the-future/" target="_blank">first ponderings</a> of CEO, Dick Reed seven years ago, to today, where it is a vital part of our agency’s offerings and a key component to nearly all of our client’s campaigns.</p>
<p>Let’s take retail for example. In an <a href="http://www.mediahorizons.com/blog/item/441-6-location-based-mobile-marketing-tactics" target="_blank">article</a> published by Marketing Land Inc, retail sales lift 7.5% when mobile marketing is incorporated. Specifically, retargeting users from desktop to mobile can be helpful to keep your brand at the top of mind. Adding the programmatic tactic of cross-device targeting, you have the ability to track a potential customer browsing plants on their desktop so that the next time they’re near a nursery or garden center, you could send them a relevant coupon on their mobile device, making them more likely to convert.</p>
<p>Our industry has mostly mastered the Desktop retargeting secret sauce that would make even In N Out blush. So, naturally the next frontier to master is mobile programmatic. As technology changes the mobile landscape and users spend more time on their mobile devices, the ability to target the right users, at the right place, at the right time, and with the right message will be even more crucial.</p>
<p>Advertising evolves as consumer behavior evolves. Those who understand and embrace this notion will ultimately be the most successful.</p>
<p><strong>Amy Recuero<br />
</strong><strong>Just Media, Inc.</strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com/2015/07/mobile-marketing-the-new-king/">Mobile Marketing: The New King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://justmedia.com">Just Media, Inc.</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://justmedia.com/2015/07/mobile-marketing-the-new-king/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
